Guide to Records of the Office of the President (John Brademas) RG.3.0.10
New York University Archives
- Series XIII. Speeches and Writings, 1981-1991; 54394; 22.50 Linear Feet in 54 manuscript boxes.; 1 audiocassette; 3 videocassettes (vhs)
  - Dinner in Honor of David Kriser and Annette Weiner Dinner (NYU), 1985-10-01; 55287 (Box 276, Folder 22)
  - Remarks by L. Jay Oliva, University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1985-10-10; 55284 (Box 276, Folder 23)
  - Alumni Staff Reception (NYU), 1985-10-16; 55283 (Box 276, Folder 24)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU) RESTRICTED, 1985-10-21 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - Convocation for Prime Minister Peres of Israel (NYU), 1985-10-21; 55281 (Box 276, Folder 25)
  - 50th Anniversary of Courant Institute of Mathematical Sciences (NYU), 1985-10-22; 55280 (Box 276, Folder 26)
  - Stephen and Beatrice Brademas Lecture, Ball State University (Muncie, IN), 1985-10-24; 55279 (Box 276, Folder 27)
  - Convocation for Alfred Gottschalk (NYU), 1985-10-28; 55278 (Box 277, Folder 1)
  - Testimony on PL 94-142, Hearing of the Subcommittee on the Handicapped, Committee on Labor and Human Resources (Washington, D.C.), 1985-10-29; 55277 (Box 277, Folder 2)
  - Higher Education Capital Finance Symposium (New York, NY), 1985-10-31; 55276 (Box 277, Folder 3)
  - Central Opera Service National Conference (New York, NY), 1985-11-01; 55275 (Box 277, Folder 4)
  - The Rita and Stanley H. Kaplan Center Dinner Dance (New York, NY), 1985-11-06; 55274 (Box 277, Folder 5)
  - The Ernest J. and Elena A. Bruno Memorial Lecture Re: Healthcare (New York, NY), 1985-11-07; 55273 (Box 277, Folder 6)
  - Testimony at a Hearing of the Subcommittee on Postsecondary Education and Labor, on the 20th Anniversary of the Higher Education Act (San Marcos, TX), 1985-11-08; 55271 (Box 277, Folder 7)
  - School of Business and Public Administration Annual Charles Waldo Haskins Associates Dinner (NYU), 1985-11-11; 55270 (Box 277, Folder 8)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1985-11-14; 55272 (Box 277, Folder 9)
  - School of Dentistry Fall Alumni Day (NYU), 1985-11-15; 55269 (Box 277, Folder 10)
  - Real Estate Institute Breakfast (NYU), 1985-11-18; 55267 (Box 277, Folder 11)
  - Dedication of the Dr. Louis Blatterfein Center for Preclinical Sciences at the NYU Dental Center, 1985-11-18; 55268 (Box 277, Folder 12)
  - Yale Club (New York, NY), 1985-11-19; 55266 (Box 277, Folder 13)
  - Chet Huntley Dinner and Lecture (NYU), 1985-11-20 (Box 277, Folder 14)
  - Remarks Regarding International Education at American Universities, Brademas' Induction into the Academy of Athens (Athens, Greece), 1985-11-26; 55265 (Box 277, Folder 15)
  - Don Forman Mini-Gym Dedication (NYU), 1985-12-03; 55264 (Box 277, Folder 16)
  - Memo Re: Graduate Education Issues Relating to the Reauthorization of the Higher Education Act, 1985-12-04; 55263 (Box 277, Folder 17)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1985-12-09 (Box 277, Folder 18)
  - Mainstream / Church Society International Recognition Banquet (New York, NY), 1985-12-10; 55262 (Box 277, Folder 19)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration Conference on Not-For-Profit Sector (NYU), 1985-12-11; 55261 (Box 277, Folder 20)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1985-12-12; 55260 (Box 277, Folder 21)
  - Fundraising Campaign Lunch (NYU), 1985-12-17; 55259 (Box 277, Folder 22)
  - Dynamis Annual Christmas Dinner (San Francisco, CA), 1985-12-20 (Box 277, Folder 23)
  - Briefing on NYU Highlights for Ted Fiske Interview (NYU), 1986-01-06; 55258 (Box 277, Folder 24)
  - Presentation of Award of Honor for Art and Culture to Helen Frankenthaler (New York, NY), 1986-01-06; 55257 (Box 277, Folder 25)
  - Starr Foundation / Nussenzweig Press Conference (NYU), 1986-01-07; 55256 (Box 277, Folder 26)
  - Highlights of the Presidency of John Brademas at New York University, 1986-01-10; 55255 (Box 277, Folder 27)
  - Symposium on Budget Balance (New York, NY), 1986-01-10; 55254 (Box 277, Folder 28)
  - Friends of Nancy Hanks Center Interview (New York, NY), 1986-01-13; 55253 (Box 277, Folder 29)
  - School of Continuing Education Paul McGhee Medal Lecture and Dinner (NYU), 1986-01-13; 55252 (Box 278, Folder 1)
  - Dinner Honoring Dean Ed Kaufman (NYU), 1986-01-16; 55251 (Box 278, Folder 2)
  - Puerto Rico Residence Center Commencement (San Juan, PR), 1986-01-18; 55250 (Box 278, Folder 3)
  - NYU Alumni of the Virgin Islands Reception (Saint Thomas, U.S. Virgin Islands), 1986-01-19 (Box 278, Folder 4)
  - Institute of Fine Arts Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1986-01-29 (Box 103, Folder 6)
  - Introduction of Edward Muskie, Lecturer at the Center for National Policy (NYU), 1986-01-30; 55248 (Box 278, Folder 5)
  - Various Alumni Events in Florida, 1986-02-01; 55247 (Box 278, Folder 6)
  - First All-University Florida Alumni Day Brunch (Hollywood, FL), 1986-02-02; 55246 (Box 278, Folder 7)
  - Dinner for Gerald Corrigan (NYU), 1986-02-05; 55245 (Box 278, Folder 8)
  - Draft Press Release on FY 87 Budget (NYU), 1986-02-07; 55244 (Box 278, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee of the Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1986-02-10 (Box 103, Folder 7)
  - Dinner for Margaret Atwood (New York, NY), 1986-02-12; 55242 (Box 278, Folder 10)
  - Draft Position Paper on Education at Colloquium Sponsored by the Anti-Defamation League and Woodrow Wilson Center, 1986-02-19-1986-02-20; 55241 (Box 278, Folder 11)
  - Urban Research Center Press Conference (NYU), 1986-02-24; 55240 (Box 278, Folder 12)
  - Metro Center Benefit Lunch (NYU), 1986-02-25; 55239 (Box 278, Folder 13)
  - Message from the President -- NYU Magazine Essay, March 1986; 55238 (Box 278, Folder 14)
  - "Building Toward the 21st Century: The Challenges of Higher Education," NYU Annual Report from the President, 1986-03; 55237 (Box 278, Folder 15)
  - Afternoon at Washington Square (NYU), 1986-03-02; 55236 (Box 278, Folder 16)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1986-03-04 (Box 103, Folder 8)
  - Great Artists Series Honoring Louise Nevelson, Guggenheim Museum (New York, NY), 1986-03-05; 55234 (Box 278, Folder 17)
  - International Relations Study Center (NYU), 1986-03-05; 55233 (Box 278, Folder 18)
  - National Book Critics Circle Awards Ceremony (NYU), 1986-03-06; 55232 (Box 278, Folder 19)
  - School of Business and Public Administration Conference on the Future of American Business -- Introduction of President Gerald Ford (NYU), 1986-03-07; 55231 (Box 278, Folder 20)
  - International Celebration Lecture (NYU), 1986-03-10 (Box 278, Folder 21)
  - Presidential, University and Education Scholars Breakfast (NYU), 1986-03-11; 55229 (Box 278, Folder 22)
  - New York Delegation Breakfast (Washington, D.C.), 1986-03-12; 55228 (Box 278, Folder 23)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1986-03-13; 55227 (Box 278, Folder 24)
  - Association for Children and Adults with Learning Disabilities International Conference (New York, NY), 1986-03-13; 55226 (Box 278, Folder 25)
  - 33rd Annual Graduate School of Business Administration Business Conference (NYU), 1986-03-15; 55225 (Box 278, Folder 26)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1986-03-17 (Box 103, Folder 9)
  - Real Estate Institute Urban Leadership Award Dinner (New York, NY), 1986-03-19; 55223 (Box 278, Folder 27)
  - Visiting Group of United States Information Agency (USIA) Officials (NYU), 1986-03-24; 55222 (Box 278, Folder 28)
  - Triangle Fire Memorial Rally (NYU), 1986-03-25; 55221 (Box 278, Folder 29)
  - Third Olive Branch Awards Ceremony (New York, NY), 1986-03-25; 55220 (Box 278, Folder 30)
  - Mayor's Press Conference on the School of Education, Health, Nursing, and the Arts Professions (NYU), 1986-03-26; 55218 (Box 278, Folder 31)
  - Tisch School of the Arts Press Lunch Honoring Yuri Lyubimov and Zelda Fichandler, 1986-03-26 (Box 278, Folder 32)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1986-04-01 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Movie Screening -- Spain: Ten Years After… (NYU), 1986-04-02; 55216 (Box 278, Folder 33)
  - Various Events (Florence, Italy), 1986-04-03; 55215 (Box 278, Folder 34)
  - Presentation of the C. Walter Nichols Award to Felix Rohatyn (NYU), 1986-04-03; 55214 (Box 278, Folder 35)
  - Touro College Convocation (Huntington, NY), 1986-04-13; 55213 (Box 278, Folder 36)
  - Lunch for Westchester Guidance Counselors (NYU), 1986-04-14; 55212 (Box 278, Folder 37)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions Dean's Cabinet Dinner, 1986-04-14 (Box 278, Folder 38)
  - Constantine Trypanis Dinner (NYU), 1986-04-15; 55211 (Box 278, Folder 39)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1986-04-17; 55210 (Box 278, Folder 40)
  - Founders Day Honors Convocation (NYU), 1986-04-17; 55209 (Box 278, Folder 41)
  - All-University Alumni Branch Meeting (Washington, D.C.), 1986-04-18; 55208 (Box 278, Folder 42)
  - "Scholarship and Public Policy," Library of Congress Symposium (Washington, D.C.), 1986-04-18; 55207 (Box 279, Folder 1)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration Dean's Day (NYU), 1986-04-19; 55206 (Box 279, Folder 2)
  - Luncheon for Roger Penrose (NYU), 1986-04-23; 55205 (Box 279, Folder 3)
  - A Nation at Risk Conference (Salt Lake City, UT), 1986-04-26; 55204 (Box 279, Folder 4)
  - "The Values of Higher Education," Davies Forum Public Lecture (San Francisco, CA), 1986-04-28; 55203 (Box 279, Folder 5)
  - Alerdinck East-West Media Conference IV Lunch (NYU), 1986-05-02; 55202 (Box 279, Folder 6)
  - National Commission on Excellence in Educational Administration New York Seminar (NYU), 1986-05-08; 55198 (Box 279, Folder 7)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1986-05-08; 55197 (Box 279, Folder 8)
  - Annual School of Commerce and School of Business and Public Administration Dinner (NYU), 1986-05-08; 55196 (Box 279, Folder 9)
  - Henry R. Ferrettie Memorial Dinner (Mishawaka, IN), 1986-05-10; 55195 (Box 279, Folder 10)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU) RESTRICTED, 1986-05-12 (Box 103, Folder 11)
  - Testimony at a Hearing of the Subcommittee on Select Revenue Measures of the Committee on Ways and Means Re: Faculty Housing (Washington, D.C.), 1986-05-12; 55193 (Box 279, Folder 11)
  - Spanish Civil War Symposium (NYU), 1986-05-14; 55192 (Box 279, Folder 12)
  - Annual Heights Colleges Awards Dinner (NYU Club), 1986-05-16; 55191 (Box 279, Folder 13)
  - Avery Fisher Center Dedication (NYU), 1986-05-19; 55190 (Box 279, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Broadcasters Seminar (NYU), 1986-05-21; 55189 (Box 279, Folder 15)
  - Leo Jaffe Theatre Dedication (NYU), 1986-05-21 (Box 279, Folder 16)
  - New York State Honorary Fire Chiefs Association 35th Anniversary Dinner (New York, NY), 1986-05-21 (Box 279, Folder 17)
  - Dean Jill Claster Reception (NYU), 1986-05-27 (Box 279, Folder 18)
  - Annual Dinner Meeting for the New York Alliance for the Public Schools (NYU), 1986-05-27; 55188 (Box 279, Folder 19)
  - Trustees Dinner Celebrating Honorary Degree Recipients (NYU), 1986-06-04; 55187 (Box 279, Folder 20)
  - NYU Commencement, 1986-06-05; 55186 (Box 279, Folder 21)
  - School of Medicine Last Day Exercises (NYU), 1986-06-05; 55185 (Box 279, Folder 22)
  - Introduction of Governor Michael Dukakis (New York, NY), 1986-06-06; 55184 (Box 279, Folder 23)
  - Hellenism Videotape Script, 1986-06-06 (Box 279, Folder 24)
  - Reception for School of Continuing Education Summer Writers Conference Scholarship Winners (NYU), 1986-06-10; 55183 (Box 279, Folder 25)
  - Urban Research Center Forum on State Economic Development Policy (NYU), 1986-06-17; 55182 (Box 279, Folder 26)
  - Reception for the University Athletic Association (NYU), 1986-06-23; 55181 (Box 279, Folder 27)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration Conference for Health Managers (NYU), 30 June 1986; 55180 (Box 279, Folder 28)
  - Art News Magazine Interview (New York, NY), 1986-07-02; 55179 (Box 279, Folder 29)
  - Commentary Piece for Social Education (New York, NY), 1986-07-02; 55178 (Box 279, Folder 30)
  - Liberty Weekend Conference (New York, NY), 1986-07-06; 55177 (Box 279, Folder 31)
  - Breakfast for the Delegation of Chinese University Presidents, 1986-07-10 (Box 279, Folder 32)
  - Dinner for the Delegation of Chinese University Presidents (NYU), 1986-07-12; 55176 (Box 279, Folder 33)
  - Essay on Education in 2011 A.D. for American Banker, 1986-07-22; 55175 (Box 279, Folder 34)
  - "Congressional Politics, Special Interests and Foreign Policy" at Salzberg Seminar (Salzburg, Austria), 1986-08-12; 55174 (Box 280, Folder 1)
  - Harvard Symposium on Liberal Learning (Cambridge, MA), 1986-09-03; 55173 (Box 279, Folder 2)
  - Harvard-Epworth Church Service (Cambridge, MA), 1986-09-07; 55172 (Box 280, Folder 3)
  - Background Material for Meeting with Ned Schnurman (New York, NY), 1986-09-08; 55171 (Box 280, Folder 4)
  - Washington Square Park Task Force and Coalition Meeting (NYU), 1986-09-11; 55170 (Box 280, Folder 5)
  - Student Convocation (NYU), 1986-09-15; 55169 (Box 280, Folder 6)
  - "The Value of Public Service," Brookings Institute Conference (Washington, D.C.), 1986-09-16; 55168 (Box 280, Folder 7)
  - Introduction of Terry Sanford at a Breakfast at the Regency Hotel (New York, NY), 1986-09-16; 55167 (Box 280, Folder 8)
  - Time Magazine Distinguished Speakers Program -- Corazon Aquino (NYU), 1986-09-19; 55166 (Box 280, Folder 9)
  - Executive Committee Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1986-09-22 (Box 103, Folder 12)
  - Lotos Club Dinner (New York, NY), 1986-09-22; 55165 (Box 280, Folder 10)
  - Alumni Council Meeting (NYU), 1986-09-22; 55163 (Box 280, Folder 11)
  - Graduate School of Business Administration Overseers Dinner (NYU), 1986-09-25; 55162 (Box 280, Folder 12)
  - "The Value of Liberal Arts," Franklin Pierce College (Rindge, NH), 1986-09-27; 55161 (Box 280, Folder 13)
  - New York City School Volunteer Program, 1986-09-30; 55160 (Box 280, Folder 14)
  - Medical Center Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1986-10-02 (Box 103, Folder 13)
  - Nancy Hanks Center Dedication (Washington, D.C.), 1986-10-06; 55158 (Box 280, Folder 15)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1986-10-09; 55157 (Box 280, Folder 16)
  - Sir Curtis Keeble Dinner (NYU), 1986-10-15; 55156 (Box 280, Folder 17)
  - Salute to Committee for the Year 2000 (New York, NY), 1986-10-14 (Box 280, Folder 18)
  - Breakfast for Orientation Leaders (NYU), 1986-10-16; 55155 (Box 280, Folder 19)
  - Florida Alumni Leader Organizational Luncheon (Miami Beach, FL), 1986-10-19; 55153 (Box 280, Folder 20)
  - 127th Annual Session of the American Dental Association (Miami Beach, FL), 1986-10-19; 55154 (Box 280, Folder 21)
  - NYU School of Dentistry Alumni in Florida Breakfast (Miami Beach, FL), 1986-10-20; 55151 (Box 280, Folder 22)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1986-10-20 (Box 103, Folder 14)
  - Press Conference to Temporarily Close Washington Square Park (New York, NY), 1986-10-22; 55150 (Box 280, Folder 23)
  - "Is the Agenda for Science Too Important to be Left to Scientists?", Sigma Xi Centennial Annual Meeting (Washington, D.C.), 1986-10-25; 55149 (Box 280, Folder 24)
  - NYSERNet Press Conference (NYU), 1986-10-28; 55148 (Box 280, Folder 25)
  - The New York Times Interview Re: NYU Board of Trustees, 1986-10-29; 55147 (Box 280, Folder 26)
  - Reception for Returning Students, 1986-10-29; 153075 (Box 280, Folder 27)
  - "The American Economy: The Political Dimension", 92nd St. Y, 1986-10-29; 55146 (Box 280, Folder 28)
  - Dedication for the William S. and Frances B. Todman Center for Film and Television (NYU), 1986-10-30; 55145 (Box 280, Folder 29)
  - Dentistry Alumni Convocation (NYU), 1986-10-31; 153073 (Box 280, Folder 30)
  - Institute of Fine Arts Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1986-11-05 (Box 103, Folder 15)
  - School of Business and Public Administration Charles Waldo Haskins Dinner Honoring John C. Whitehead (New York, NY), 1986-11-05; 55143 (Box 280, Folder 31)
  - Tribute Letter to Louis Koenig, 1986-11-07; 55141 (Box 280, Folder 32)
  - The Fulbright Alumni Association of Greater New York (New York, NY), 1986-11-08; 55140 (Box 281, Folder 1)
  - Parents Day (NYU), 1986-11-09; 55139 (Box 281, Folder 2)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1986-11-13; 153072 (Box 281, Folder 3)
  - Sir Ernst Gombrich Lecture (NYU), 1986-11-17; 55137 (Box 281, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Science 100th Anniversary Convocation (NYU), 1986-11-19; 55135 (Box 281, Folder 5)
  - Introducing Honorary Degree Recipients at a Dinner Honoring the 100th Anniversary of the Graduate School of Arts and Science (NYU), 1986-11-19; 55136 (Box 281, Folder 6)
  - "Tax Reform in America: The Impact on Higher Education," 15th Annual Business Symposium Sponsored by St. Peter's College (Jersey City, NJ), 1986-11-19; 55134 (Box 281, Folder 7)
  - School of Business and Public Administration and Graduate School Board of Overseers Meeting RESTRICTED, 1986-11-20 (Box 103, Folder 16)
  - John Douglas Scanlan Dinner, 1986-11-25; 55132 (Box 281, Folder 8)
  - Neil Gordon Kinnock Dinner (NYU), 1986-12-01; 55131 (Box 281, Folder 9)
  - New York Times President's Forum (New York, NY), 1986-12-02; 153071 (Box 281, Folder 10)
  - Humanities Council 10th Anniversary Lecture, Saul Bellow Introduction (NYU), 1986-12-04; 55130 (Box 281, Folder 11)
  - Sports and Recreation Development Committee Meeting (NYU), 1986-12-05; 55129 (Box 281, Folder 12)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting (NYU) RESTRICTED, 1986-12-08; 153070 (Box 103, Folder 17)
  - Essay Re: Federal Support for Higher Education for Scholarship and Public Policy -- Humanities Council, 1986-12-09; 55127 (Box 281, Folder 13)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1986-12-11; 55125 (Box 281, Folder 14)
  - Department of Hebrew and Judaic Studies Dinner (NYU), 1986-12-11; 55126 (Box 281, Folder 15)
  - New York Times Interview Re: Claire Flom and the Alliance, 1986-12-11; 55124 (Box 281, Folder 16)
  - "Meanwhile Greece Goes on Traveling…", Nicholas E. Christopher Memorial Lecture in Modern Greek Studies (Cambridge, MA), 1986-12-12; 55123 (Box 281, Folder 17)
  - Dinner Honoring Major Donors (NYU), 1986-12-16; 55122 (Box 281, Folder 18)
  - NYU Faculty Council, 1986-12-18; 153068 (Box 281, Folder 19)
  - "Scholarship and Public Policy", New York Public Library Lecture (New York, NY), 1987-01-06; 55121 (Box 281, Folder 20)
  - NYU Medical Center Board of Trustees RESTRICTED, 1987-01-06; 153067 (Box 103, Folder 18)
  - Highlights of the NYU Presidency of John Brademas, 1987-01-10; 55119 (Box 281, Folder 21)
  - Op-Ed Response to Forbes Magazine Article by Peter Brimelow, 1987-01-23; 55118 (Box 281, Folder 22)
  - Sigma Xi of Terre Haute Reception (Terre Haute, IN), 1987-01-26; 55117 (Box 281, Folder 23)
  - "Scholarship of Public Policy" University Speaker Series (Terre Haute, IN), 1987-01-26; 55116 (Box 281, Folder 24)
  - Presidential Message for NYU Staff Handbook, 1987-01-27; 55115 (Box 281, Folder 25)
  - "The Role of Congress in Foreign Policy: Reflections of a Former Congressman", Indiana State University (Terre Haute, IN), 1987-01-27; 55114 (Box 281, Folder 26)
  - Indiana State University Founders Day Ceremony (Terre Haute, IN), 1987-01-27; 55113 (Box 281, Folder 27)
  - Institute of Fine Arts Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1987-01-28; 153066 (Box 103, Folder 19)
  - National Book Critics Circle Awards Ceremony (NYU), 1987-01-29; 55111 (Box 281, Folder 28)
  - WABC Talk Radio "Reach for Speech" Show Interview (New York, NY), 1987-02-01; 55110 (Box 281, Folder 29)
  - Journal of International Law and Politics Symposium: Trade Sanctions and International Relations (NYU), 1987-02-05; 55109 (Box 281, Folder 30)
  - "National Priorities in Higher Education," National Association of Independent Colleges and Universities Annual Meeting (Washington, D.C.), 1987-02-06; 55108 (Box 282, Folder 1)
  - Executive Committee Meeting RESTRICTED, 1987-02-09; 153064 (Box 103, Folder 20)
  - Testimony, Hearing of the Committee on Education and Labor (Washington, D.C.), 1987-02-10; 55106 (Box 282, Folder 2)
  - Oxford Piece -- NYU Report, 1987-02-11; 153063 (Box 282, Folder 3)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1987-02-12; 153062 (Box 282, Folder 4)
  - Citizens Committee, New Yorker for New York Awards (New York, NY), 1987-02-12; 55105 (Box 282, Folder 5)
  - "Is the Agenda for Science too Important to be Left to Scientists?" Sigma Xi Article for American Scientist, 1987-02-15; 55103 (Box 282, Folder 6)
  - Anti-Drug Effort, Washington Square Park, 1987-02-17; 153053 (Box 282, Folder 7)
  - Consulate-General of the People's Republic of China (New York, NY), 1987-02-17; 55102 (Box 282, Folder 8)
  - Democratic National Committee National Finance Council Winter Meeting (Newport Beach, CA), 1987-02-21; 55101 (Box 282, Folder 9)
  - NYU AIDS Mental Health Project Press Conference (NYU), 1987-02-24; 55100 (Box 282, Folder 10)
  - Lecture by Giovanni Spadolini, NYU Law School, 1987-02-25; 153061 (Box 282, Folder 11)
  - 2nd Annual Petrie Lecture in Entrepreneurship and Dinner (NYU), 1987-02-26; 55098 (Box 282, Folder 12)
  - "International Education: A Matter of Survival," Article for Education Record, 1987-02-27; 55097 (Box 282, Folder 13)
  - University Article by Brademas on Oxford, England, 1987-03; 55096 (Box 282, Folder 14)
  - Lunch for Peter Lax (NYU), 1987-03-03; 55094 (Box 282, Folder 15)
  - Medical Center Board Meeting RESTRICTED, 1987-03-04 (Box 103, Folder 21)
  - Dinner for Trustees, Deans, Faculty and Administration Hosted by David Kriser (NYU), 1987-03-04; 153060 (Box 282, Folder 16)
  - Scholars Day (NYU), 1987-03-08; 153059 (Box 282, Folder 17)
  - Afternoon at Washington Square (NYU), 1987-03-08; 55092 (Box 282, Folder 18)
  - NYU in Albany Reception (Albany, NY), 1987-03-09; 153058 (Box 282, Folder 19)
  - NYU in Albany Alumni Reception (Albany, NY), 1987-03-09; 55091 (Box 282, Folder 20)
  - Trustee Financial Meeting RESTRICTED, 1987-03-09; 153057 (Box 103, Folder 22)
  - Presidential, University and Educational Scholars Breakfast (NYU), 1987-03-10; 55089 (Box 282, Folder 21)
  - Metro Center Benefit Luncheon (NYU), 1987-03-10; 55090 (Box 282, Folder 22)
  - "NYU: University in the City," New-York Historical Society (New York, NY), 1987-03-11; 55088 (Box 282, Folder 23)
  - University Senate Meeting (NYU), 1987-03-12; 55086 (Box 282, Folder 24)
  - "Modern Role of Congress," Association of the Bar Forum (New York, NY), 1987-03-12; 55087 (Box 282, Folder 25)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting RESTRICTED, 1987-03-16 (Box 103, Folder 23)
  - Introduction of Mario Cuomo at Arms Control Forum (NYU), 1987-03-16; 55084 (Box 282, Folder 26)
  - Press Conference for "Due Case, Una Tradizione" Project (NYU), 1987-03-16; 55083 (Box 282, Folder 27)
  - Graduate School of Public Administration Dean's Day (NYU), 1987-03-16; 55082 (Box 282, Folder 28)
  - Lynne Cheney Press Luncheon and Dinner (NYU), 1987-03-16; 55081 (Box 282, Folder 29)
  - Dinner Honoring Lady Mary Warnock (NYU), 1987-03-17; 55080 (Box 282, Folder 30)
  - Real Estate Institute Urban Leadership Award Dinner (NYU), 1987-03-18; 55079 (Box 282, Folder 31)
  - Hoosiers Movie Dinner (NYU), 1987-03-19; 55078 (Box 282, Folder 32)
  - Chicago Alumni Reception, 1987-03-26; 153052 (Box 283, Folder 1)
  - Meetings with Alumni in Chicago and Los Angeles, 1987-03-26-1987-03-29; 55077 (Box 283, Folder 2)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies -- Convocation Materials (NYU), 1987-03-30; 153051 (Box 283, Folder 3)
  - Onassis Center For Hellenic Studies Press Conference and Dinner (NYU), 1987-03-30; 55076 (Box 283, Folder 4)
  - Onassis Center for Hellenic Studies Announcement, Convocation (NYU), 1987-03-30 (Box 101, Video 35)
  - Gallatin 15th Anniversary Dinner (NYU), 1987-03-31; 153046 (Box 283, Folder 5)
  - "Scholarships and Public Policy," Essay for Book on the Humanities, 1987-04-01; 55075 (Box 283, Folder 6)
  - NY Science Policy Association (New York, NY), 1987-04-01; 55074 (Box 283, Folder 7)